♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
♪
New shirt, Cleveland?
Donna saw an unflattering
picture of me on Facebook
and only lets me wear black now.
Is the picture that bad?
It was the worst thing
I would ever want
to see myself be.
Problem with these dark shirts
is the dandruff shows.
But when I wear light colors...
The dandruff doesn't show, but
you look bigger in the shirt.
-Yeah, it's called
"Guillermo's Paradox."
-What's that now?
Guillermo del Toro theorized
that a fat man's shirt
cannot simultaneously appear
slimming and clean.
Mm. That boy does look
like he be gettin' dry.
All right, Peter,
what's going on?
Well, truth be told,
Meg wants me to give her
a bunch of money
so she can go to college,
and I guess...
I guess I'd rather spend
that money on alcohol.
Listen, I helped
my daughter through college
and it was the best thing
I ever did.
Well, it was just
kind of us talking, but how so?
Right after she graduated,
she got a real good job
and bought me a new car.
Says she's gonna buy me
a house one day,
so I can sell this place
and retire.
Man, imagine how great
it would feel to be retired?
I knew a retired kid
in high school.
All he ate was Tater Tots.
He smooshed a turtle
like a ice cream sandwich.
-He was severely retired.
-Okay, Peter.
Guys, I've got to help Meg get
into a good college.
Then I can have the golden years
I've always dreamed of.
I sure am gonna miss you, baby.
New wife that's just
one giant freckle?
Come on, Florida, cancer,
let's go!
(Brian barking)
What's going on? You okay?
This-this squirrel, man...
(squirrel chittering)
Yeah, come down here
and do it, huh?
Come down here!
Well, you're getting old, Bri.
Might be time to pack it up
and get out
of the squirrel gettin' game.
No way, man. That little
bastard comes down here...
Hey.
(chittering)
Get him, boy.
-♪
-(Brian barking)
(panting)
(retches)
You've got to get in shape, man.
You know,
you should meet my trainer.
I think you'd really like him.
-You have a trainer?
-Yes.
You think it's easy
looking zero for 20 years?
All right, fine,
I'll give it a shot.
Right now I feel more useless
than a chiropractor
in an emergency.
Excuse me,
is anyone here a doctor?
I have a heating pad
in my office.
What seems to be the problem?
(cheering)
♪
All right, Meg,
now if we're gonna get you
into a good school,
we're gonna have
to fudge your application a bit.
Okay, how do we do that?
I don't know, I ate the fudge.
But the good news is
I got a letter of recommendation
for you.
It's from Big Bird
and I wrote it.
-"When I first met..."
-Read it as Big Bird, please.
(nasally):
"When I first met Peter,
I was impressed at how tall
and handsome he is."
That's coming from Big Bird?
Think of all the celebrities
he's met.
Ryan Reynolds was
on  Sesame Street.
-Wow.
-"Also, have you ever noticed
"that Grover
and Super Grover are never
in the same room
at the same time?"
As I said, Lois,
not two days ago.
♪
Principal Shepherd,
what's it gonna take
to get Meg into a college?
If Meg has any chance at all,
she's going to need
a little "extra help."
We'll do anything.
Whatever it takes.
Good. Now you do
understand how this works?
We understand.
I guess I'll, uh,
I'll meet you in the car.
He didn't mean you have
to sleep with him.
There are a few options.
♪
(lights buzzing)
Now, Mr. And Mrs. Griffin,
every college
has spots set aside
for athletic recruits.
We can make Meg look
like a star athlete.
With the click of a button,
we can make Meg look like
she played varsity lacrosse,
won the Quahog Marathon,
or had her head
roll down a temple
in Apocalypto.
♪
Lois, this is amazing!
Meg's gonna look more successful
than a businessman
in a hard hat.
Hey! I came down here from the
office to point at the plans,
then at the building!
Plans! Building!
Building! Plans!
Yes, sir. Right away, sir!
MAN (singing):
I come down to the site
once in a while.
♪
Hi, uh, you must be
Stewie's trainer.
Wh... How did you...? I thought
I was gonna meet your trainer?
You're looking at him, Bri.
Look at my body.
I'm jacked.
You want to get jacked?
-Uh...
-Yeah, you want to get jacked.
That's what having a trainer is.
Just a couple of guys
getting jacked.
-Sometimes twice a day.
-Okay, you know what...?
All right, before we start in,
a little business to go over.
I was just messing around about
the jacked stuff, by the way.
Uh, did you want to sign up
for the full three years?
Three years? Don't you just
do it by the session?
Yeah, no, we can do,
uh, sesh to sesh.
Not committed.
Did you want to do
the supplement plan?
Uh. uh, no. No, thanks.
Going through the motions.
All right, so what do you
got going on for New Years?
-What?
-80% of being a trainer is
asking clients what
they're doing for New Years.
And then not seeming interested
when you tell me.
I don't know, I might go
over to a buddy's house
and watch the ball drop.
Oh, right on.
-So, uh, what do you do
for work?
-I'm a writer.
-Okay, so lot of sittin'?
-Yeah.
Hang on, I got to make a call.
Hey, Death? I got a guy here
just about ready for you.
No, not really,
I'm just trying to make a point.
All right,
and that is it for today.
First sesh in the books.
Let's Ven' to the 'mo.
♪
CLEVELAND:
♪ Mail time, mail time,
mail time, mail time ♪
♪ Mail time. ♪
The mail's here!
♪ Here's the mail
that never fails ♪
♪ It makes me want
to wag my tail ♪
♪ When it comes
I want to wail mail... ♪
"To Meg Griffin."
(gasps)
It's from Brown!
I've been accepted!
Hey, that's great news.
Let's clap it up
my high school girlfriend
and I still say
I love you in e-mails.
I was hoping the good news
and the clapping
would offset this secret.
But yay, Meg!
♪
Wow, I remember when my parents
clapped their hands
after moving something one time.
You never forget those moments.
Now remember, Meg, I want you
to call us every week,
and then every few weeks,
and then never.
I promise, Mom.
Got to admit, I'm kind of
jealous you get to go
to college
and live in such a cool dorm.
Look, they even have the
pay phone Denise Huxtable
would call from
on A Different World.
Hi, Dad. College is great.
I'm doing what I want
to actresses
and will get support
from my wife Camille.
That stuff was more out
in the open than I remember.
(indistinct chatter)
Well, I guess that's it.
Our baby is all grown up
and living at college.
I know! She's so lucky!
This place is awesome!
You think I'll go
to college one day?
Oh... yeah.
Sky's the limit, champ.
Lois, I'll meet you down
at the car.
I got to take a dump
that will live on
in story and song.
No, I don't have a roommate.
I guess he, like,
died or something.
So I've got a double
all to myself.
A double? Hey, roomie.
Want to listen to The Doors
for the next six months
and then never again
for the rest of your life?
Wait, you're my roommate?
You're Ashok Chandrasekhar?
-God bless you.
-(laughs)
Classic Ashok.
♪
Hey, why'd you tell me
to meet you at Meg's room?
Well, now that Meg is
in college,
I turned her room into a gym.
Oh, my God.
-How'd you do this?
-Took a Limitless pill
and played "Old Town Road"
on loop.
All right, why don't we
start off with a plank?
One minute, and I'm gonna
go call my girlfriend
and the forget about you.
And... go.
-(phone beeps)
-Hey.
-I'm at the gym, why?
-Stewie?
Babe, you know I can't deal
with your sister.
Hey, babe... babe? Baby girl?
-Stewie!
-Babe! Babe, I'm not--
baby babe,
ba-babe, baby, baby, come on.
-(sharp snap)
-(shouts, moaning)
-Babe, I'll call you back.
(moaning)
Okay, right on, so you
remember I was telling you
about the magnesium supplement
with the bone boost?
So this is why you want
to try and take that.
-Right on?
-No, not "right on"!
My arm feels like it's broken!
Oh, it's gonna need some P.T.
Let me give you the card
of my physical therapist.
He's the best.
This is gonna be you
in another shirt, isn't it?
Hey, what's the problemo?
Give me the rundown, go ahead.
♪
H-Hey, Meg?
Hi, I'm Xander.
I'm-I'm in your bio class.
I'm not a stalker.
(laughs)
Either way.
Listen, me and my roommates
are having people over tonight,
and I was wondering
if you'd want to come by.
Yeah. I'd love to.
Awesome.
Keeney, 325.
PETER:
Heads up!
(Meg exclaims)
Dad? What the hell
are you doing?
I'm going to college now.
Wait, what? What about Mom?
Well, I had to have
a tough conversation
with her by the lake.
♪
I'm just not a fan
of long-distance relationships.
Peter, I need to know
if you're gonna
pick Stewie up from school.
I'll be home for Thanksgiving.
We'll see where we're at then.
(indistinct chatter)
Hi, I'm Serena.
This is Lily and Grace.
-Weet up.
-Hyai.
Are you interested in pledging
for Alpha Delta Pi?
Yeah! I hear you guys throw
all the best parties.
ALL:
Well, we've been waiting
for you all summer,
and we're so glad
you're finally here.
(all screaming happily)
GIRLS (chanting):
Boom, boom, I wanna
go A D Pi...
PETER:
Meg, you gotta
get me out of here.
These people are
out of their minds.
Do not go A D Pi, Meg.
Do not join this thing.
They don't let us out
of the pile.
They're so mean, Meg.
They're so mean.
SORORITY SISTERS:
I wanna go A D Pi,
don't you?
Hey, Meg, I'm a hippie now,
and I'm feeling the burn.
-Bernie Sanders?
-No, none of my
hippie girlfriends shower,
and my crotch itches.
You know, despite what
we're doing here,
-I'm still your daughter.
-Right, right.
Hey, uh, would you sign
this petition
to help save the spotted owl?
-Yeah, sure.
-Awesome.
You're our 50th signature.
So what happens now?
Buck, wait!
-(chain saw revs)
-Buck!
They got 50 signatures.
That's 50 all right.
Well, let's get back
in the truck.
♪
You don't have to
be afraid anymore.
I'm still itchy.
MEG:
Dad, I'm holding the ladder!
♪
There he is, the big dog.
You ready to sweat?
Today we got legs, and I'm
gonna tell you everything
I've ever watched on Netflix.
Stewie, listen, I don't want you
to take this the wrong way,
but I got a new trainer.
New trainer? Who?
Doug? Ugh.
That's right, Stewie,
it's an ugh-Doug moment.
No hard feelings.
I think Brian here
just wants to rev up
-to a higher octane.
-See you around, Stewie.
So it might take me a little
longer to train you, Brian.
You're going to have to unlearn
everything Stewie taught you.
Fortunately, that was
almost nothing.
(Brian laughs)
Oh, man.
♪
PETER:
Heads up.
Ow! Dad, what the hell?
Did you join a frat?
I tried to, but I got
the letters mixed up
and joined a fart.
(flatulence)
(laughs)
Hey, everyone, I'm in college,
but here's a test for you.
We just gave you
the easiest joke setup
in Family Guy history:
Peter joins a fart house.
Is the correct punchline A?
B?
Or C?
Good luck to you.
And now back to our story.
Hey, ladies, toga farty tonight
at I Delta PU.
-Tell your friends.
-Ew, no.
Heh, they all say that.
-Hey, what are you reading?
-Boning up for an exam.
I boned up yesterday when
I walked into the girls' shower.
(classic slide whistle riff)
Dad, please!
Sorry, Meg, I've been smoking
doobies all morning.
Talk about higher education.
(classic up-down slide)
That's it.
I can't take this anymore.
Dad, get out of here.
What? This is what college is.
How do you know?
You're not even a student here.
You're a total fraud.
Me? You wouldn't even be here
if your mother and I didn't
-pay someone to get you in.
-What?!
Yeah, your whole application
was fake.
Meg, is this true?
What? No, of course not,
Dean Nearby.
Well, if it is,
you're going to be suspended.
Oh, no.
Well, that weekend on the Cape
with Principal Shepherd
was a waste.
I know I said
I wouldn't get clingy,
but when can I
see you again?
I can't believe
they suspended Meg.
Suspended Meg? Peter, you and I
could be going to jail.
I can't go to jail.
Me and my fart brothers
are supposed to streak
the quad later.
(plays "Charge" riff)
Now stop that.
You're not in
whatever you think
college is anymore.
I can't believe you two
did this to me.
Maybe if you believed in me,
none of this would have
happened.
Meg, honey, nobody wanted you
out of this house
more than we did.
You know, maybe there's a way
none of you gets in trouble.
What are you talking about?
Well, you said you can do
all those things
on your application.
If you show you actually can
do those things,
you're all in the clear.
And then I can get back to
hustling drunk women upstairs
with Tobin and Squee.
Well, I better get to work,
then.
But I seriously doubt that
I'll be able to pull this off.
Hey, come on.
Anything's possible.
Like when that Starbucks cup
made it onto Game of Thrones.
This is it.
Here it comes, here it comes.
-Hey!
-Oh, my gosh.
-That's so cool.
I can't believe this.
What's the Internet saying?
They-they thought
you were great.
Okay, Brian, this many.
-(straining)
-This many.
Come on, Brian, you can do it.
(straining)
And that's as many as I know.
Good job, Brian.
Hey, Stewie,
congratulate your friend.
He just did this many sit-ups.
What? There's nothing
after that.
-That's as high as it goes.
-(chuckles) Yep.
Are you crazy,
pushing him that hard?
You're playing a dangerous game.
Yeah, it's dangerous.
And that's the way I like it.
Listen, Doug, I've been
meaning to talk to you.
I just got this new job,
and the commute is... ugh.
I can work around
your schedule.
Well, that's the thing.
I don't have one.
That's the way the suits
figured it anyway.
What exactly is this job?
I know, right?
Anyway, you've been terrific,
and I'm gonna keep at this.
But I'm afraid this is goodbye.
What if I went down
to $300 a week?
-STEWIE: You're paying him?!
-I'm sorry.
(blows raspberries)
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
There's no need for that.
(blows raspberries)
-Thank you for that, Brian.
-You're welcome, Stewie.
You know, this whole thing has
taught me an important lesson.
I hate exercise.
Gay-men.
Somebody has to help me
walk down the stairs.
♪
MAN (through bullhorn):
Everyone, if I could have
your attention.
I'm Dean Distant Faraway,
and we're here today
to determine whether or not
Meg Griffin can justify
her admission to our university.
-And we're Mom and Dad. Hi.
-Go blue.
DISTANT FARAWAY:
What did they say?
I-I'm very far away.
♪
Strike.
(all cheering)
Ah... Dr. Nassar?
-(whispers indistinctly)
-(gasps) Oh, my stars.
Okay, I'm gonna try to kill
two birds with one stone here.
I'll be singing
"Love is a Battlefield"
-by Pat Benatar.
-(murmuring)
In Russian.
(excited chatter)
-Hit it.
-(music starts)
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ My sil'nyy ♪
♪ Nikito Nam Ne Skazhet chto ♪
♪ My ne pravy ♪
♪ Dolgo ishchen vy ♪
♪ Nashix serdtsa ♪
♪ My oba znaem chto ♪
♪ Lyubov eto battlefield. ♪
(cheering)
Well, it appears you can do
pretty much everything
you claimed on your application.
So that's it?
I'm back in school?
I think all you have to do now
is prove you can
windsurf over Providence Falls.
Oh, right.
You prove that, you're back.
Wait, did we check that she can
get dunked on by her dad?
Dunked on by my d...?
Oh!
You gotta get big, Meg.
(cheering)
Guys, no matter what happens,
I just want you to know
that I forgive you
for what you did.
I know deep down you were
just looking out for me.
Whatever you think
the lesson is here
is fine by us.
(fanfare plays)
Good luck, Meg.
We love you.
(crowd cheering)
♪
(breathes deeply)
Aah...
Aw, so close.
(crowd screaming)
(Meg yelling)
Peter, call an ambulance.
Can you do it?
My number's blocked by 911.
Come on, you can do this.
Stewie does it every day.
-He does?
-Yep.
Just put one hand on the rail.
Damn it, I can't.
Uppies.
Adios, Doug.
From hell's heart
I stab at thee.
With my last breath,
I spit upon...
(snoring)
Ha! What a baby.